Land of the fathers, the guides, the noble
And fortress of the Book which shall not be subdued
O Mauritania, spring of concord
And pillar of forbearance, portal of peace
We shall protect your borders, we are your ransom
And we paint your hills with the colour of hope
And when you call, we answer forthwith
The constellations of your skies have not been veiled
And the sun of your forehead has not set
We suckled the milk of praise from Yarab
For Africa, the sweetest source
We have taken you as a covenant, we have carried you as a promise
And we shall give you happiness for a generation that has come of age
Land of the fathers, the guides, the noble
And fortress of the Book which shall not be subdued
O Mauritania, spring of concord
And pillar of forbearance, portal of peace
And when you call, we answer forthwith